Article	Date	Heading	NewsType
KARACHI: The Sindh government has decided to bring down public transport fares by 7 per cent due to massive reduction in petroleum product prices by the federal government	01/01/15	sindh govt decides to cut public transport fares by 7pc kti rej	business
HONG KONG: Asian markets started 2015 on an upswing in limited trading on Friday with mainland Chinese stocks surging in Hong Kong on speculation Beijing may ease monetary policy to boost slowing growth.	01/02/15	asia stocks up in new year trad	business
KARACHI: Strong bulls on Friday pulled the benchmark KSE-100 Index at Karachi Stock Exchange (KSE) and taking it across the psychological barrier of 33000 points with a single days gain of 207 points.	01/09/15	bullish kse jumps over 33000 psychological barrier	business
Singapore: Oil fell further in Asia Monday with weak demand and a supply glut putting relentless pressure on prices already at their lowest in five and a half years	01/12/15	oil falls further in asian trad	business
KARACHI: Wholesale market rates for sugar dropped to less than Rs 50 per kg following the resumption of sugar cane crushing by sugar mills in Sindh.	13/01/15	sugar prices drop to rs 49.80 in sind	business
Cape Town: Ben Stokes and Jonny Bairstow tore apart the South African bowling attack as they enjoyed a run feast at Newlands on a record-breaking second day of the second Test which led to England declaring their first innings on 629 for six.	01/03/16	England declare on 629 6 on record breaking day	sports
HONG KONG:  Hong Kong shares opened 0.66 percent lower Monday following a tepid lead from Wall Street  as the first full week of the new year kicked off.The benchmark Hang Seng Index dipped 158.63 points to 23.	01/05/15	hong kong stocks open 0.66 percent lower	business
New York: Oil prices tumbled Tuesday to fresh 5.5-year lows as Saudi Arabia blamed weak global economic growth and said it will stick to its guns on production policy.	01/07/15	oil hits new 5.5 year lows as saudis defend 	business
CAPE TOWN: Ben Stokes scored the second fastest double century in Tests and led a run feast on the second day of the second Test against South Africa by battering the home attack to take England to 513 for five wickets at lunch.	01/03/16	Stokes batters South Africa in blistering double 	sports
SYDNEY: Carlos Brathwaite shone briefly for West Indies but the rain was the only real winner on Monday as wet weather washed away all but 11.2 overs of play on the second day of the third Test against Australia.	01/04/16	Brathwaite cameo a bright spot in Sydney washou	sports
HONG KONG: Asian markets tumbled Tuesday following painful losses in New York and Europe while the euro sat near nine-year lows as political uncertainty in Greece fanned renewed fears it could leave the eurozone.	01/06/15	asian stocks sink euro near nine year 	business
NEW YORK: US oil prices Monday slipped below $50 a barrel for the first time in more than five years as the surging dollar and news of additional supplies extended a six-month rout.	01/06/15	us oil prices slip below 50 a barr	business
CAPE TOWN: Jonny Bairstow pumped his chest to the sky and wiped away a tear as he completed an emotional maiden test hundred for England against South Africa on Sunday	01/04/16	Tearful Bairstow enjoys best day of his lif	sports
CAPE TOWN: England grabbed three wickets in 23 balls to inject life back into the second Test but any hopes they had of skittling South Africa out were ended by Temba Bavuma on Tuesday.	01/05/16	Bavumas rapid fifty halts England reviv	sports
MUMBAI: Maharashtra schoolboy Pranav Dhanawade rewrote the record books on Tuesday	01/05/16	Indian schoolboy breaches 1000 run mark in an inning	sports
SYDNEY: Australia have withdrawn from the under-19 World Cup in Bangladesh later this month because of concerns over the safety and security of the squad	01/05/16	Australia withdraw from U 19 WC in Banglad	sports
London: Pakistan Yasir Shah made a useful unbeaten 30 after starring with the ball to leave Pakistan well-placed come stumps on the third day of an intriguing first Test against England.	16/07/16	Yasir stars with bat despite Woakes heroi	sports
LONDON: Yasir Shah took the best innings figures by a visiting spinner against England in a  Test innings in more than a century as Pakistan strengthened their grip on the series opener.	16/07/16	Yasir Shah leaves England in a spi	sports
KARACHI: State Bank of Pakistan kept its key policy rate unchanged at 5.75 percent on Saturday	30/07/16	State Bank keeps policy interest rate 575 	business
Karachi: Pakistan stocks ended at a record high on Monday after State Bank of Pakistan left interest rates unchanged last week.	08/01/16	Pakistan stocks end record hig	business
LONDON: Pakistan captain Misbah-ul-Haq followed his first-innings hundred with a duck as England fought back on the third day of the first Test at Lord.	16/07/16	Misbah out for nought as England fight b	sports
LONDON: Pakistan Yasir Shah took six for 72 against England on Saturday to become just the fifth leg-spinner to take six wickets in a Test innings at Lord	16/07/16	Yasir Shah in elite Lords company	sports
Islamabad: International financial market analysis firm BMI says that Pakistan will be developed as manufacturing hub over the coming years.	08/01/16	Pakistan will be among top 10 emerging markets from Asia BMI	business
LAHORE: Pakistan Cricket Board (PCB) Chairman Shahryar Khan on Tuesday said Yasir Shah's family suffers from blood pressure disease and the leg-spinner consumed some of the medicine to control his blood pressure.	01/05/16	Yasir Shah takes blood pressure medicine Shahryar	sports
CAPE TOWN: Captain Hashim Amla remained unbeaten after his third Test double century as South Africa moved closer to forcing a draw against England in the second Test at Newlands on Tuesday.Amla was 200 not out at lunch with Faf du Plessis (81) at the other end	01/05/16	Amla leads South Africas reply with double 	sports
ISLAMABAD: The Jewellary exports from the country increased by 28.78 percent during the fiscal year 2015 to 16 compared to the corresponding period of last year.The overall exports of jewellry from the country during July June (2015 16) were recorded at 8.492 million compared to the exports of 6.594 million in July June (2014 15) according to Pakistan Bureau of Statistics (PBS).	08/01/16	Pakistan Jewellary exports up 29 FY16	business
Tokyo: Tokyo stocks opened lower Monday  despite a mostly solid lead from Wall Street after the Bank of Japan last week disappointed investors with or 153.96  to open at 16 points underwhelming tweaks to its stimulus programme. The benchmark Nikkei 225 index slipped 0.93 percent	08/01/16	Tokyo stocks open lower after BoJ under	business
SYDNEY: Australia spinners Nathan Lyon and Stephen Keefe took key wickets between rain showers to peg West Indies back to 207 for six at the end of a weather-disrupted opening day of the dead rubber third Test on Sunday.	01/03/16	Australias spinners peg West Indies back in Sydney rai	sports
CAPE TOWN: Captain Hashim Amla scored an unbeaten century on the third day of the second Test against England and AB de Villiers made 88 as South Africa reached tea on 290 for three on Monday.Amla scored his first hundred for more than a year and De Villiers reached 8000 Test runs.	01/04/16	Amla makes century De Villiers falls for 88	sports